Sianong!
-Come on, let's go!
-Let's go!
-Ouch!
-Let's go.
Agent Alex, what's the meaning of that?
Is it about Mikoy?
Is that because of them?
At last.
Get inside. We're here.
Take a seat.
Slowly, Angelito.
Drink this.
Thank you.
-I want to say thank you.
-For what?
For taking the bullet.
You didn't have to do that.
I did that because you're
a part of our team.
Damn it!
Looks like we got played.
They led us the wrong way.
Come on. Let's go back!
Hey, take it easy.
-Thanks.
-Sianong, the gun.
-Why?
-Brusko, stay there.
-I'll stay here.
-Wait.
Oh.
It's just a wild boar.
What did you say?
Just a wild boar.
A wild boar?
-Yes!
There.
Still nothing?
Come on.
Unbelievable.
This wild boar you cooked is delicious!
Brother, you're ready to get married!
Okay.
Try over here.
I think this is better.
It really won't work, sweetheart.
Come on.
You know what?
Let's just conserve our batteries.
Right?
You're right.
And for when someone answers.
So we can keep contacting them.
You know, I can use the car's battery.
I can bypass it.
Not to brag,
but when it comes to technology,
I'm your guy.
Maybe we're just too deep
inside the farmland.
But our biggest problem is the transmitter
and the antenna.
Like this one.
It's broken.
No matter how loud you shout,
no one will hear you, Sir Mikoy.
We still don't trust you.
But I want out of here.
Don't you want a signal too?
I can't focus
with the two of you staring at me.
It's making me nervous.
We don't care.
That's what I thought.
Can you hurry up?
Hey, are you sure about this?
No!
About 98%.
-Yes.
-You're not helping.
Ma'am, that's pretty high for a tech guy.
Agent Dara, we got something!
Are you talking to that?
Ma'am, trust me.
It's more responsive than most people.
Trust me.
Here we go.
We lost it!
Mikoy.
-No, no, no, no.
-Guys.
-Just keep it up.
My armpit is killing me!
Higher! Higher!
-Don't move.
-Okay.
Still nothing.
Come on, give me a signal.
Give me a signal.
You said you wouldn't leave me.
Good grief.
Come on, Angelito.
I just went to the bathroom,
and you disappeared.
You're so clingy.
I was just looking for a signal.
I was going back anyway.
Go on. Head back.
You might get hurt out there.
I'm okay.
You might overexert yourself.
See?
I've already taken my medicine.
See? I'm feeling much stronger now.
Fine, suit yourself.
We will enter here.
Let's head there.
-Yes, just relay it to them as well.
-Thank you, ma'am.
Right. Just let them know too.
Sir, it's Sir Mario.
-Sir Mario.
-Good evening.
Mario.
Norberto.
Let's talk first.
Are you sure you don't
need me for this operation?
Absolutely sure.
We need you at the safe house.
It's important that you're there.
Besides, Tess is probably
worried sick about you,
and I have confidence in Sofie.
They say she's just like me.
Resourceful,
a little stubborn at times,
brave, never backs down.
But as time goes by,
without any news from the island,
I can't sit still.
It feels like I can barely breathe
because I'm so worried.
That's how I feel about my sons too.
Even though they're grown men,
I lose all my bravado
when their lives are on the line.
Any father
in your position would do the same.
Whether they've served or not.
Norberto, I know
your priority is to save
your team and Sofie,
but I have one favor to ask.
Bring Angelito and Mikoy home.
They need to make it back safely for Tess.
You have my word. I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
Are you sure?
So it does work!
And you made me climb up earlier.
You know,
I saw the way you looked
at that bomb earlier.
I know how badly you wanted it.
I know you could have.
But you didn't.
And I also know the old Chiara
wouldn't have thought twice.
It was easier back then.
Back then, all I worried about
were Mom and Dad.
Things are different now.
Thank you, sweetheart.
But we still didn't win.
We didn't get the bomb.
And we still haven't found Angelito.
-Mikoy.
-I found him.
I found my brother.
Then I lost him again.
If I did not leave--
It's not your fault.
It's not Sianong's fault,
and it's not Sofie's either.
We're just having bad luck today.
As salty as the sea.
But we'll find them.
Trust me.
What makes you so sure?
Because I have no choice.
When you're the older brother,
you can't afford to lose hope.
You can't give up
until you know for sure that they're safe.
We'll find them.
All of them.
Chiara.
When all of this is over,
I just want to chase children.
Three.
-Three right away?
-Yes!
Just imagine,
two little Mikoys and one little Chiara.
Right?
Wouldn't that be cute?
Why only one little Chiara?
That would be dangerous, sweetheart.
Just imagine,
two troublemakers and one hothead.
Oh, man!
That'd be chaos.
Excuse me. I'm not always angry.
All right, all right.
Two troublemakers
and one…
passionate one!
Better?
You're getting my hopes up.
About what?
That.
Having kids?
Because I want that too.
Angelito.
Do you think they got it?
The bomb?
Maybe.
I guess.
It's not your fault, Sofie.
But…
I just couldn't help it.
Sofie.
Thank you for…
for staying by my side.
asking for help.
Thank you for guiding me.
Earlier…
All day.
Thank you for not leaving me.
Even if I was so weak.
Don't mention it.
Oh, come on.
The other day,
I was like your mom, and now,
you're thanking me like I'm your grandma.
Don't.
Sianong.
Don't leave me.
Please, don't leave me.
Please don't leave me!
He's burning up.
Believe me.
Sianong.
Believe me, believe me.
I've been looking for you.
I never…
I never got tired of you.
No, I never gave up.
And now…
now…
you're here.
No one will ever separate us ever again.
No one, no one. Stay here with me.
-Sianong.
-My god.
Please, my love.
Can you ever forgive me?
Sianong.
If we stay here any longer without rescue,
he won't make it.
How are we supposed to get rescued?
We need to find another way.
We're already struggling to get a signal.
How are we supposed to reach the agency?
If only we had a ninja messenger like W.M.
The one who secretly delivered
the message to Donabel and Viktor.
That was so cool.
So sneaky.
What's W.M.?
W.M.
Winnie the Mooh.
Seriously, you've been doing this all day.
Wild boar, Winnie the Mooh.
Will you just shut up?
Especially you.
Shut up with your nonsense
if you're not helping.
You asked for it.
Go get some water.
I know that voice!
Sianong!
Sianong.
Wait, Sofie…
Angelito.
Angelito!
Angelito, not now.
Angelito.
Angelito, wait.
The worst part is we don't have much time.
We can't do anything!
That's not the Chiara I know.
The Chiara I know is always
up to something.
Always mission accomplished.
After all that, she will leave
everything behind.